>> Kyle Simpson: 记住 BigInts，它们是基本类型。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Remember BigInts,
they're a primitive type.
因此，当您使用文字 ( 例如，第 2 行 ) 指定 BigInt 时，
So when you assign a BigInt using
a literal, for example like line 2,
42 号不光 42号但在这个空间里有 42 个
42n is not just the number 42, but it's
42 within this space where it can grow
本质上是无穷大的，直到系统上的内存空间。
essentially infinitely large, up to
the memory space on the system, of course.
它本质上可以有一个无限大的整数。
It can essentially have an integer
that grows infinitely large.
那是另外一个分区
That's a separate partition,
它不是一个 IEEE 号码，就像所有 JavaScript中的其他数字。
it's not an IEEE number like all
the other numbers in JavaScript.
你必须非常谨慎因为 BigInts 和常规号码
And you have to be very careful,
because BigInts and regular numbers,
他们的混合和配合也不太好
they don't really mix and match that well.
他们完全是分开的如果你愿意的话
They're totally separated things,
if you will.
如果我们有个东西看起来很有用的话
And so it's gonna be really useful for
us if we have a thing that looks
就像一个数字要确定一个数字，还是一个 BigInt?
like a number to determine is
that a number, or is it a BigInt?
这就是为什么打字机至少现在
Which is why typeof,
at least at the moment,
将返回我们的字符串 BigInt。
is slated to return us the string, BigInt.